const deck = [
    {
      id: "easy",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing sensory information from the body?",
      answer: "Somatosensory cortex"
    },
    {
      id: "medium",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for regulating sleep and wakefulness?",
      answer: "Hypothalamus"
    },
    {
      id: "medium",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing language?",
      answer: "Broca's area"
    },
    {
      id: "hard",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for initiating and controlling voluntary movement?",
      answer: "Primary motor cortex"
    },
    {
      id: "easy",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for regulating thirst and hunger?",
      answer: "Hypothalamus"
    },
    {
      id: "hard",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing and interpreting visual information?",
      answer: "Visual cortex"
    },
    {
      id: "medium",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for regulating emotions and motivation?",
      answer: "Amygdala"
    },
    {
      id: "easy",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for controlling breathing and heartbeat?",
      answer: "Brainstem"
    },
    {
      id: "hard",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for integrating sensory information and coordinating movement?",
      answer: "Cerebellum"
    },
    {
      id: "medium",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing and storing memories?",
      answer: "Hippocampus"
    },
    {
      id: "easy",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for regulating body temperature?",
      answer: "Hypothalamus"
    },
    {
      id: "hard",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for executive functions such as decision-making and planning?",
      answer: "Prefrontal cortex"
    },
    {
      id: "medium",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing auditory information?",
      answer: "Auditory cortex"
    },
    {
      id: "easy",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for controlling balance and coordination?",
      answer: "Cerebellum"
    },
    {
      id: "hard",
      question: "What is the part of the brain responsible for processing olfactory information?",
      answer: "Olfactory bulb"
    }
  ]

export default deck;
  